[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "How does that work now with this decision?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "that", "work", "now", "with", "this", "decision", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Yes, that can happen.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "that", "can", "happen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Do you think he will feel justice was served?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "will", "feel", "justice", "was", "served", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Oh, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "Did Ravi's tweets nail him?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "Ravi", "'s", "tweets", "nail", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "I think they did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ravi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "So, when we look back one day at this like it was Brown versus Board of Education for social media, will this be a precedent, Lisa?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "when", "we", "look", "back", "one", "day", "at", "this", "like", "it", "was", "Brown", "versus", "Board", "of", "Education", "for", "social", "media", ",", "will", "this", "be", "a", "precedent", ",", "Lisa", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "MD", "DT", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "This is only a trial decision.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "only", "a", "trial", "decision", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Board of Education"], "PERSON": ["Brown", "Lisa?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "NNS", "VBP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "You want to explain?", "question_tokens": ["You", "want", "to", "explain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Most states do have hate crime laws.", "answer_tokens": ["Most", "states", "do", "have", "hate", "crime", "laws", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RBS", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "Kids who are bullied, kids who are bullies, what should we as parents be telling their children?", "question_tokens": ["Kids", "who", "are", "bullied", ",", "kids", "who", "are", "bullies", ",", "what", "should", "we", "as", "parents", "be", "telling", "their", "children", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "VB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "The most importance thing I tell parents, not what they tell themselves.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "most", "importance", "thing", "I", "tell", "parents", ",", "not", "what", "they", "tell", "themselves", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "Did Ravi try to apologize but we think the message never got to Clementi?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "Ravi", "try", "to", "apologize", "but", "we", "think", "the", "message", "never", "got", "to", "Clementi", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "He -- there's some conversation he had with him that still is unknown.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "--", "there", "'s", "some", "conversation", "he", "had", "with", "him", "that", "still", "is", "unknown", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ravi", "Clementi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "How you guys doing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "you", "guys", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Doing great.", "answer_tokens": ["Doing", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Doesn't she look wonderful, man?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "n't", "she", "look", "wonderful", ",", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "She's beautiful.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "beautiful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "ALL: Together doing an interview?", "question_tokens": ["ALL", ":", "Together", "doing", "an", "interview", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Doing an interview like this.", "answer_tokens": ["Doing", "an", "interview", "like", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "How did you meet?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "meet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "Well, I saw -- you know, we were at a party, at a club, and we had just finished final exams.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "saw", "--", "you", "know", ",", "we", "were", "at", "a", "party", ",", "at", "a", "club", ",", "and", "we", "had", "just", "finished", "final", "exams", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "What was the dance back then?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "dance", "back", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "Back then, you go to the freak or you go down to the floor, and she could really do it.", "answer_tokens": ["Back", "then", ",", "you", "go", "to", "the", "freak", "or", "you", "go", "down", "to", "the", "floor", ",", "and", "she", "could", "really", "do", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "She could drop it like it was hot before you were dropping it like it was hot?", "question_tokens": ["She", "could", "drop", "it", "like", "it", "was", "hot", "before", "you", "were", "dropping", "it", "like", "it", "was", "hot", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "You want to take it from there, baby?", "question_tokens": ["You", "want", "to", "take", "it", "from", "there", ",", "baby", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "EX", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Well, you know, after we met, we went on our separate ways.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "after", "we", "met", ",", "we", "went", "on", "our", "separate", "ways", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Did he have a specific reputation as a ladies' man?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "have", "a", "specific", "reputation", "as", "a", "ladies", "'", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Not yet.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "But what was it about, that conversation?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "was", "it", "about", ",", "that", "conversation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "I think, Arsenio it was just the way she carried herself.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", ",", "Arsenio", "it", "was", "just", "the", "way", "she", "carried", "herself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "Right?", "question_tokens": ["Right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "And, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["And", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "But I watched you.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "I", "watched", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "Why did you play it that way?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "play", "it", "that", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "Come on, man.", "answer_tokens": ["Come", "on", ",", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "Was there a moment where you looked at him, and felt -- I could go the distance with this man?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "there", "a", "moment", "where", "you", "looked", "at", "him", ",", "and", "felt", "--", "I", "could", "go", "the", "distance", "with", "this", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Well, you know what it was, it was comfort, there was a comfort level.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", "what", "it", "was", ",", "it", "was", "comfort", ",", "there", "was", "a", "comfort", "level", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Back then?", "question_tokens": ["Back", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "Twice?", "question_tokens": ["Twice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "Twice, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Twice", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "Do you remember either of the reasons for calling the engagement off?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "either", "of", "the", "reasons", "for", "calling", "the", "engagement", "off", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "What did he do wrong?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "he", "do", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "No, he didn't do anything wrong.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "did", "n't", "do", "anything", "wrong", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Am I saying it right?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "saying", "it", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Where were you when he first told you that he was HIV positive?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "were", "you", "when", "he", "first", "told", "you", "that", "he", "was", "HIV", "positive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "We were at home in our office, in our den area, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "were", "at", "home", "in", "our", "office", ",", "in", "our", "den", "area", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Denver"]}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "He was supposed to be playing and you get a call from a guy who should be in the warm-up doing layups?", "question_tokens": ["He", "was", "supposed", "to", "be", "playing", "and", "you", "get", "a", "call", "from", "a", "guy", "who", "should", "be", "in", "the", "warm-up", "doing", "layups", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Yes, he was like in Denver or somewhere, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "he", "was", "like", "in", "Denver", "or", "somewhere", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "What was that ride like to her, to give her this news?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "that", "ride", "like", "to", "her", ",", "to", "give", "her", "this", "news", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "TO", "PRP$", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Arsenio, the worst ride of my life, because when you make a mistake, it actually hurts other people.", "answer_tokens": ["Arsenio", ",", "the", "worst", "ride", "of", "my", "life", ",", "because", "when", "you", "make", "a", "mistake", ",", "it", "actually", "hurts", "other", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Now, you had just found out like two days ago?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "you", "had", "just", "found", "out", "like", "two", "days", "ago", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Right, Cookie?", "question_tokens": ["Right", ",", "Cookie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "What did you do in that moment when he said it to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "do", "in", "that", "moment", "when", "he", "said", "it", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "Well, first of all, I was like, devastated.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "was", "like", ",", "devastated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "NNP", "CD", "POS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "People joked about it, but nobody really you knew really had it, you know?", "question_tokens": ["People", "joked", "about", "it", ",", "but", "nobody", "really", "you", "knew", "really", "had", "it", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "In the movie -- ESPN 33's announcement, I think there's a moment where you joked and said, I thought maybe he wanted a divorce.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "the", "movie", "--", "ESPN", "33", "'s", "announcement", ",", "I", "think", "there", "'s", "a", "moment", "where", "you", "joked", "and", "said", ",", "I", "thought", "maybe", "he", "wanted", "a", "divorce", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "CC", "JJ", ",", "NN", ",", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "You had no idea?", "question_tokens": ["You", "had", "no", "idea", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "No, we had such a hard time, back and forth, engagement, getting married.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "we", "had", "such", "a", "hard", "time", ",", "back", "and", "forth", ",", "engagement", ",", "getting", "married", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "Like a \"Days of Our Lives\" soap opera tap?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "a", "``", "Days", "of", "Our", "Lives", "''", "soap", "opera", "tap", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "``", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "A little harder than that.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "little", "harder", "than", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Did you even feel it?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "even", "feel", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "Dr. Ho, he's the acclaimed researcher of AIDS in this country?", "question_tokens": ["Dr.", "Ho", ",", "he", "'s", "the", "acclaimed", "researcher", "of", "AIDS", "in", "this", "country", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "And by the way, all of this happened because of an insurance medical test?", "question_tokens": ["And", "by", "the", "way", ",", "all", "of", "this", "happened", "because", "of", "an", "insurance", "medical", "test", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Did you lose friends?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "lose", "friends", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "No, not really.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "EX", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Never an argument?", "question_tokens": ["Never", "an", "argument", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "But there were problems.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "there", "were", "problems", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "You know what I mean?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", "I", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "It's amazing.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "amazing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "Huh?", "question_tokens": ["Huh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Larry"]}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "Tell me about this play?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "about", "this", "play", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "Well, it's going to be a play about Larry and I, our life on the basketball court and away from the court as well.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "a", "play", "about", "Larry", "and", "I", ",", "our", "life", "on", "the", "basketball", "court", "and", "away", "from", "the", "court", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Arsenio"]}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "What would make you look in the opposite direction from that sport and say, I want that now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "make", "you", "look", "in", "the", "opposite", "direction", "from", "that", "sport", "and", "say", ",", "I", "want", "that", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "I think I'm -- Arsenio, I'm a big baseball fan.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "'m", "--", "Arsenio", ",", "I", "'m", "a", "big", "baseball", "fan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "Where did that come from?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "did", "that", "come", "from", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "I created this jean for a women with curves.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "created", "this", "jean", "for", "a", "women", "with", "curves", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "So I thought why not create a jean with that style, with those styling, with the premium qualities, that fit a woman with a curve?", "question_tokens": ["So", "I", "thought", "why", "not", "create", "a", "jean", "with", "that", "style", ",", "with", "those", "styling", ",", "with", "the", "premium", "qualities", ",", "that", "fit", "a", "woman", "with", "a", "curve", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBG", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "When a woman is frustrated and it's your wife, you as the husband get that frustration.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "a", "woman", "is", "frustrated", "and", "it", "'s", "your", "wife", ",", "you", "as", "the", "husband", "get", "that", "frustration", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "Go online, you have a website?", "question_tokens": ["Go", "online", ",", "you", "have", "a", "website", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "Yes, CJByCookieJohnson.com.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "CJByCookieJohnson.com", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 677, "question": "Do you think it changed politics forever?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "changed", "politics", "forever", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "Without a doubt it changed politics forever.", "answer_tokens": ["Without", "a", "doubt", "it", "changed", "politics", "forever", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "Don't you think so?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "you", "think", "so", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "Well, let me answer the question, then I have one for you.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "me", "answer", "the", "question", ",", "then", "I", "have", "one", "for", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 717, "question": "Piers, my question to you is how did you pull it off?", "question_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "my", "question", "to", "you", "is", "how", "did", "you", "pull", "it", "off", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 718, "answer": "Well, at that time, because he was a governor, I didn't really see the magnitude of what could happen.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "at", "that", "time", ",", "because", "he", "was", "a", "governor", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "really", "see", "the", "magnitude", "of", "what", "could", "happen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 757, "question": "Why is politics so mean this year?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "politics", "so", "mean", "this", "year", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNS", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 758, "answer": "The country is fractured and the Republican party, at the moment, is fractured into a number of different groups.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "country", "is", "fractured", "and", "the", "Republican", "party", ",", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "is", "fractured", "into", "a", "number", "of", "different", "groups", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]